masterstudies.com 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy

**About the Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy explains when and why we collect information about you, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.

We, Keystone Academic Solutions AS, act as ‘’controller’’ of the personal data you provide through our websites Masterstudies.com, Bachelorstudies.com, Phdstudies.com, Mbastudies.com, Lawstudies.com, Healthcarestudies.com, Onlinestudies.com, Academiccourses.com, Studenttests.com, Studentshub.com and similar websites. This also includes all local and international domains.

Keystone Academic Solutions AS also acts as a “processor’’ on behalf of schools using our platform. Schools are using the software platform to follow up on your requests for information.

**What information do we collect?**

You may navigate on our webpage without providing your personal data except for your IP-address and user agent string. IP-address and user agent string are stored for 24 months. 

However, if you wish to receive information pertaining to us, or to receive information from the universities registered on our webpage, we will need your personal information.

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. You must be at least 16 years of age to use our services. You may be asked to enter your: Name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or educational information.

The legal basis for the processing of web form data is _contract_.  
The legal basis for the processing of optional services is _consent_ (for example newsletters).

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**What do we use your information for?  **

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * _To answer your request to a school:_ Your personal information will be processed in order to send you information about our schools educational offers from which you have requested such information.
  * _To personalize your experience:_ Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * _To improve our website:_ We process information about you when you send us e-mails directly. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To improve customer service:_ Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * If you agree to receive such information, _to send periodic emails._
  * If you agree to receive such information, _to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature._
  * If you agree to receive such information, information and updates pertaining to your request, in addition to occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information etc.

You may opt-out at any time by clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of our emails or by logging in to your student area at <https://www.studentshub.com/>. You may also unsubscribe via phone or e-mail. You will find our contact details under ‘’Contacting Us’’.

**Delete or withdraw your data**

You may at any time delete your data or withdraw your consents by contacting us via phone, or e-mail or logging in to your student area at <https://www.studentshub.com/>. You will find our contact details under ‘’Contacting Us’’. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing based on the contract or consent before its withdrawal. Our contact info is stated under ‘’Contacting Us’’.

**Request access to your data**

You may at any time request access to the information we process about you by contacting us via phone, or by e-mail or by logging in to your student area at <https://www.studentshub.com/>. You may also request to have the information corrected. You may also have your personal data transferred upon request. Furthermore, you may request restriction of processing personal data or object to the processing in accordance with relevant legislation. Our contact info is stated under ‘’Contacting Us’’.

**How do we protect your information?  **

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: Hashed/salted password protection, regular software updates, backups, firewalls, best-practice database communication, role-based system access and more. We also use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely. 

**How long do we keep your information?**

Personal data will not be stored longer than necessary for the purposes for which the personal data is processed, with a maximum of 24 months. Please note that personal data may be stored for longer periods if required by applicable law or necessary to resolve disputes or to enforce our agreements.

Information that we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information.

**Do we use cookies?  **

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables our system to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and to personalize your experience. You will be asked to consent to the use of cookies when you enter our website by clicking the ‘’I agree’’ button. You may withdraw your consent at any time by altering your browser settings or logging in to your student area at <https://www.studentshub.com/>, or by phone or e-mail.

You may continue to use our service without accepting cookies, but please note that this may affect the functionality of our website negatively.

Cookies might also be set by trusted subprocessors. Please refer to the “Subprocessors” section below for information about which subprocessors that are used.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  **

We work closely with our trusted third parties, i.e. the universities listed at our webpages, to provide you with correct and updated information about educational offers. When you request information from one of our trusted third parties, the relevant university will receive your name and e-mail address and use your details to provide you with information about the curriculum and admission process, and any other information that you have requested.

The information may also be used to send you additional newsletters and e-mails, provided you have opted in to receive such information.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to other third parties your personally identifiable information. However, we may release your information when we believe release is necessary to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. Furthermore, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Will we transfer your information outside of Europe?**

As a part of the services offered to you through our websites, the information you provide to us may be transferred outside the European Union (‘’EU’’) or the European Economic Area (EEA), provided you agree to receive information from a university outside the EU/EEA. Please note that such third countries may have different levels of protection of your personal data.

If we transfer your information outside of the EU/EEA, we will take steps to ensure that appropriate security measures are taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this policy.

**What are your rights?**

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are not processing your personal data in accordance with the relevant legislation, you may file a complaint to the supervisory authority.

**Sub-processors**

Keystone Academic Solutions AS relies on a handful of third party suppliers who assist in the service we offer to you as a user. Some of these suppliers process your personal data to be able to execute the service they offer.

**Sendgrid.com:** Send emails on our behalf.  
 **SendinBlue.com:** Send emails on our behalf.  
 **Google Analytics:** Analyzes web traffic and usage of websites.  
 **Google Ad Manager:** Advertising service for showing banner ads.  
 **Google Tag Manager:** Helps us adding Google Ad Manager tags.  
 **FullContact.com:** Search engine for e-mail addresses to find basic info about a person.  
 **Zapier.com:** Transfers user request to schools CRM system. Only when requested by school.  
 **logRocket.com and Hotjar.com:** Registers how forms are filled in order to improve user experience.

Subprocessors are confirmed GDPR compliant or of equivalent standard. For more information, please see each subprocessor’s privacy policy.

**Third Party Links  **

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only  **

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions  **

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://www.masterstudies.com/Schools_and_Universities/Terms-and-Conditions.html>.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy  **

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

This policy was last modified on 04.07.2019.

**Contacting Us  **

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or the processing of personal data, you may contact us using the information below.

Rolfsbuktveien 4D  
Fornebu, Oslo 1364  
Norway  
support@masterstudies.com   
+4723227250
